

# Nguyen Van Nam

Software Developer

Date of birth: Dec 28, 1994

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 01675278509

Email: namnvse03275@gmail.com

Address: Bac Giang, Vietnam

Website: namte.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm Nguyen Van Nam a software developer with more than 1 year of experience in software development field (at FPT Software), with good knowledge of OOP. I'm a young and a passionate developer, I always looking for something new to learn. I like helping other, work well with group and I am a very careful person. I alway try to do everything with the highest attention to avoid losing any even small detail in my task.

#### **EDUCATION**

Step. 2012 - Dec 2016

**FPT University** 

Major: Software Engineering

GPA: 8.16

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2017 - Present FPT Software

C++ Developer

- Work at FGA (FPT Automotive Global) as a C++ developer

Jan 2016 - 2016

**Others** 

Developer

- I work with my friends in some web project. We gather requirement from customer then develop the website base on their requirement.

Until now we have done 3-4 project. All of our customers are very

satisfied with our performance.

April 2015 - Jan 2016

**FPT Software** 

Software Developer Main responsibilities:

- Communicate with customers and Bridge SE to get clear

requirements.

- Develop and fix bug base on requirements.

- Testing application base on requirements.

- Learned to develop software follow Agile process.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Feb 2016

The Complete Bootstrap Masterclass - Build 4 Projects

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ZL0BQ26G/

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

Feb 2017	Excellent student of Fall 2016 (FPT University)
June 2016	Honorable student of Spring 2016 Semester (FPT University)
Jan 2015	Good student of Fall 2015 Semester (FPT University)
May 2014	Good student of Spring 2014 Semester (FPT University)

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Language:	English
Programming Languages:	- C#. NET - HTML, CSS, JS - Java - C/C++ - PHP
Frameworks & platforms:	<ul><li>- ASP.NET MVC</li><li>- jQuery / Twister Bootstrap</li><li>- Entity Framework / LINQ to SQL</li><li>- Laravel</li></ul>
Database Management Systems:	- MS SQL Server,MySQL
Version Control:	- SVN, Git
Soft Skills:	- Teamwork - Business communication
Others:	- Good understanding about OOP methodologies, Agile and Scrum development process.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **FPT Software**

(April 2015 - Step. 2015)

Customer	A Japan company
Description	<ul> <li>This is a sercuity system that include three sub system to resolves complex security issues.</li> <li>The system manages usage of devices and network connections to regulate the transit of the confidential data.</li> <li>Encrypts data on hard drive, removable media,</li> </ul>
Team size	500 Man-Month
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Create design document - Optimize code

	- Bug Fixing - Testing other code
Technologies used	- C/C++, C#

## **FPT Software**

(Oct 2015 - Dec. 2015)

Customer	A Japan company
Description	- A website that manage the score of a university include the entrance exam, student
Team size	20
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Review code - Create design document - Bug Fixing - Testing other code
Technologies used	- Php, Zend framework.

## **FPT Software**

(Dec 2015 - 2016)

Customer	A Japan company
Description	- Create website for the air-port
Team size	20
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Review code - Create design document - Bug Fixing - Testing other code
Technologies used	- VB. Net

## Other

(Dec 2015 - 2016)

Customer	A office department
Description	- Create a website to manage the document inside that office
Team size	2
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analyze and Design - Development - Review code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- C# MVC 5.

# Capstone Project (Step.2016 - Dec 2016)

Customer	FPT University
Description	- We create a software that can recognize the fingerprint, verify user base on their fingerprint.
Team size	4
My position	Developer

My responsibilities	<ul> <li>- Analyze and Design</li> <li>- Development</li> <li>- Review code</li> <li>- Bug Fixing</li> <li>- Create report</li> <li>- Create design document</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- C# MVC 5. C/C++ Raspberry Pi 3 model B.